const cards = [
    {
        front:'a',
        back:'ant'
    },
    {
        front:'b',
        back:'ball'
    },
    {
        front:'c',
        back:'car'
    },
    {
        front:'d',
        back:'dog'
    },
    {
        front:'e',
        back:'egg'
    },
    {
        front:'f',
        back:'fish'
    },
    {
        front:'g',
        back:'goat'
    },
    {
        front:'h',
        back:'horse'
    },
    {
        front:'i',
        back:'ice'
    },
    {
        front:'j',
        back:'jam'
    },
    {
        front:'k',
        back:'key'
    },
    {
        front:'l',
        back:'lemon'
    },
    {
        front:'m',
        back:'monkey'
    },
    {
        front:'n',
        back:'nest'
    },
    {
        front:'o',
        back:'owl'
    },
    {
        front:'p',
        back:'pan'
    },
    {
        front:'q',
        back:'queen'
    },
    {
        front:'r',
        back:'rocket'
    },
    {
        front:'s',
        back:'snake'
    },
    {
        front:'t',
        back:'table'
    },
    {
        front:'u',
        back:'umbrella'
    },
    {
        front:'v',
        back:'vegetables'
    },
    {
        front:'w',
        back:'whale'
    },
    {
        front:'x',
        back:'xylophone'
    },
    {
        front:'y',
        back:'yacht'
    },
    {
        front:'z',
        back:'zebra'
    },

]